

# Cyril Moran

MECHANICAL ENGINEER

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A driven engineer with a passion to better our community through engineering innovation. Coupling leadership and technical skills along with professional experience, illustrate all the qualities that will make a significant difference in your company.

#### **EDUCATION**

08-2018 – 12-02022

# University of Florida, B.S of Mechanical Engineering

GPA of 3.6

- American Society of Mechanical Engineers member
- Generational Relief in Prosthetics member
- BRASA member

## 2014 - 2018 Sarasota High School, High School Diploma

- GPA of 4.6
- Cambridge AICE Diploma recipient

## **EXPERIENCE**

08-2021 - present

## **Undergraduate Researcher**

University of Florida

- Designing an overnight dialysis system
- Create an electrodialysis (ED) benchmark system in SOLIDWORKS
  - Perform CFD and Electrodialysis analysis in ANSYS on the 5-layer ED membrane for a 60% salt retention rate
- Synthesize a graphene oxide (GO) membrane that permits protein permeability
- Design a scaled 3-stage system that incorporates the GO membrane, ED system, and reverse osmosis membrane to test and troubleshoot

11-2016 – 05-2018

### **Lead Cashier**

<sup>5-2018</sup> Home Depot

- Provide customers with fast, friendly, accurate and safe service while processing transactions efficiently
- Proactively seek product/project knowledge to provide customers with information and identify selling opportunities
- Handle dissatisfied customers and customer complaints with diplomacy and guidance towards positive resolutions
- Convince customers to apply for Home Depot credit cards
  - o One of the top performers in Cashier Department.

04-2021 –

## Tutor

08-2021 Sylvan Learning Center

- Create a safe and inclusive learning environment for kids of all ages
- Teach Mathematics up to Calculus 3 and Differential Equations
- Teach Reading and Science at a college level
- Create a structure of learning for younger adolescents to develop foundational knowledge.
- Saw a 10-70% increase in students' performance on monthly aptitude tests.